[Music]
so now we have this uh artistry
skin nutritional renewing reactivation
cream so after the toner you should have
the cream itself so
um
it's not uh only a cleanser alone no
it's not only the toner alone no and
it's not only the cream so you have to
use the three
products on your skin in order to have
the best result itself
so this products
i will open this
so this is the cream so after i used the
toner i used this kind of cream
to put it on my skin just a
drop of it and just put it yeah
so i stayed the toner for about like two
minutes or three minutes before i put
the
the cream
okay
so now i have a little
piece of amount of cream on my skin and
i spread it
spread spread
okay
and here
so you can still use it on your neck
okay so it's still safe so
i just use it in my face right now
so yeah
still the smell is very good really i
really love how it smells the prada
and
that's why
i introduced this kind of product
because of the smell
is safe and
now
this is the renewing cream reactivation
so this
uh hyaluronic acid and the rosemary that
is the best ingredients that we have
inside and it's safe it still came from
um
exclusive from amway and made from usa
and the vegan
and
so you will see that if there's
a code of a wagon like that so it's safe
and it's natural and now you can see
soften my skin
and maybe when i use this for how many
months i will i will
do another video in some other point
after a month and to see the best result
right now i just used it for three days
and you will see already the result you
know it softens my skin
[Music]
smell is very good really and that's
what i like about the product so
thank you very much for watching this
blog and hopefully you like it
and you will subscribe to my channel too
and hopefully when you want to buy
something like um this kind of product
you can contact me and have some friends
to
to to send to you this kind of this this
product so we have the cleanser
the first one you use and then the toner
and then the cream so it's very best on
your skin really if you want the ageless
skin a soft especially right now that we
have a winter
season so it really helps it really
helps a lot if you want your skin to to
to stay the natural itself so thank you
so much and have a blessed blessed day
so hopefully you like my video so this
is a product from the artistry which is
made from usa and uh exclusively from
amway so thank you very much and have a
great day